wazua.co.ke 2010-12-03

# PRIVACY POLICY - Home | Wazua

**1\. Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find,we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**2\. Acceptance Privacy Policy Terms**

Please note that our Privacy Policy applies to " wazua.co.ke " only (and related subdomains). Your usage of this Web Site constitutes acceptance of this privacy policy and any modifications made to it.

**3\. Application of Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected by wazua.co.ke from the users of our community website (www.wazua.co.ke ). It does not apply to information collected by www.wazua.co.ke in any other way, including offline. 

**4\. Links**

www.wazua.co.ke contains links to other web sites operated by third parties. www.wazua.co.ke is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of such third party web sites and this Policy does not apply to those web sites.

**5\. The Information We Collect**

**a) Non-Personal Information Collected and How it is Used**  
www.wazua.co.ke is not set up to automatically collect personally identifiable information from each visitor to our www.wazua.co.ke. It does recognize the originating web server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example,we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names,addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to www.wazua.co.ke. The technical information we do collect is used only for internal purposes by our technical support staff.

www.wazua.co.ke does track certain information about the visits to our Web Site. For example, statistics showing the numbers and frequency of visitors to www.wazua.co.ke and its individual pages. These aggregated statistics are used internally to enhance www.wazua.co.ke and general marketing purposes. Those aggregated statistics may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties but contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

**b) Personal Information Collected**  
In a few areas on www.wazua.co.ke, you are asked to provide information that will enable www.wazua.co.ke to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from our www.wazua.co.ke, to enable us to enhance your www.wazua.co.ke experience, to assist you with customer service or technical support issues, to follow up with you after your visit to www.wazua.co.ke, or to otherwise support your customer relationship with www.wazua.co.ke. Providing such information is completely optional. However, failure to provide it may mean that you cannot access and use certain information, materials and services.

**6\. How We Use Personal Information**

www.wazua.co.ke uses your personal information only for specific purposes.  
The personal information you provide to www.wazua.co.ke, such as your name, postal or e-mail address or telephone number will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with www.wazua.co.ke, and to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services from www.wazua.co.ke, or offers from third parties that www.wazua.co.ke thinks may be of interest to you. Agents or contractors of www.wazua.co.ke who are given access to your personal information will be required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for www.wazua.co.ke.

www.wazua.co.ke may enhance or merge your personal information collected at www.wazua.co.ke with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

Circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties for purposes other than to support your customer relationship with www.wazua.co.ke, such as in connection with a corporate divestiture or dissolution of a portion of the owners of www.wazua.co.ke, or if disclosure is permitted or required by law (for example, in connection with judicial proceedings or gover nm ental investigations).

**7\. Opting Out or Unsubscribing**

www.wazua.co.ke will send you information about various products and services or other products or services that may be of interest to you. Only www.wazua.co.ke (or agents or contractors working on behalf of www.wazua.co.ke under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct or electronic mailings. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, you can request to be removed from either direct or electronic mailing lists at any time by emailing connect@wazua.co.ke.

**8\. www.wazua.co.ke Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy,and ensure the correct use of information, www.wazua.co.ke have put into place appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online through firewalls and encryption technology.

**9\. Amendments**

www.wazua.co.ke reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes will be posted on www.wazua.co.ke.

**10 . How to Contact Us**

If you would like to contact connect@wazua.co.ke for any reason regarding our privacy practices,to request a copy of the personal information that connect@wazua.co.ke has collected about you, or to have inaccuracies or omissions in this information corrected via the Internet, contact connect@wazua.co.ke.
